{
    "subject": "resource/Stone_Poneys",
    "predicate": "property/pastMembers",
    "object": "resource/Linda_Ronstadt",
    "human_readable": "Linda Ronstadt was a past member of Stone Poneys.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.94130539894104,
            "question": "Who was Linda Ronstadt a past member of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7971212863922119,
            "question": "Name a group that Linda Ronstadt was associated with."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7547524571418762,
            "question": "What musical group did Linda Ronstadt belong to in the past?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7313780188560486,
            "question": "Which band featured Linda Ronstadt as a member?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7250982522964478,
            "question": "Linda Ronstadt was formerly a member of what band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5340884327888489,
            "question": "Was Linda Ronstadt ever part of a band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.480112761259079,
            "question": "What was the name of the music group that Linda Ronstadt was part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4213871955871582,
            "question": "Before her solo success, with which musical ensemble was Linda Ronstadt affiliated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4155634045600891,
            "question": "In what musical group did Linda Ronstadt have an early career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27706480026245117,
            "question": "What band did Linda Ronstadt perform with before her solo career?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Linda Ronstadt was a past member of Stone Poneys.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4335_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what musical group did Linda Ronstadt have an early career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4335_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Before her solo success, with which musical ensemble was Linda Ronstadt affiliated?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4335_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the name of the music group that Linda Ronstadt was part of?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4335_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4335_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4335_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4335_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4335_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4335_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4335_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4335_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4335_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4335_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4335_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that Linda Ronstadt was a member of the Stone Poneys in the 1960s. Specifically, the document with file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4335/re-ranker-msmarco/74.txt states: \"In the mid-1960s at the forefront of California\u2019s emerging folk rock and country rock movements, Ronstadt joined forces with Bobby Kimmel and Kenny Edwards and became the lead singer of a folk-rock trio, the Stone Poneys.\" This supports the statement that Linda Ronstadt was a past member of the Stone Poneys."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}